[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which feature on a map helps determine direction?", "correct_answer": "a compass rose", "incorrect_answers": ["a key", "a legend", "a scale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete these lyrics from the theme song of a western that was on TV in the 1960s:  \nA soldier of fortune is a man called______________.\n_______________  ______________ where do you roam?.", "correct_answer": "Paladin", "incorrect_answers": ["Chester", "Johnny Yuma", "Sundance"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which radio station was the first national US broadcast made?", "correct_answer": "KDKA  in Pittsburgh", "incorrect_answers": ["KPHI in Philadelphia", "WWRL in Chicago", "WINS  in New York"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1989 Christmas movie has the tagline, They lost the true spirit of Christmas...And found it locked in the heart of one little girl.?", "correct_answer": "Prancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Miracle on 34th Street", "The Santa Clause", "The Polar Express"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The most common type of broccoli is sometimes referred to with this term in the United Kingdom.", "correct_answer": "Calabrese", "incorrect_answers": ["Romanesco broccoli", "All of these", "Cafiolli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun orbits a center of mass.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about grasshoppers?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They have salivary glands.", "Their digestive tract secretes digestive enzymes.", "They have two antennae on their heads."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these US cities is largest (by population)?", "correct_answer": "Houston", "incorrect_answers": ["Phoenix", "Philadelphia", "San Antonio"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Doctor John and Ricki Lee Jones sing this fun love song on the Sleepless in Seattle soundtrack.", "correct_answer": "Makin Whoopee", "incorrect_answers": ["Lets Do It", "Cest Si Bon", "Havana Hoochee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the prefix pithe refer to?", "correct_answer": "Ape", "incorrect_answers": ["Human", "Invertebrate", "Mammal"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Komodo Dragon is NOT native to which of these islands?", "correct_answer": "Savalhi", "incorrect_answers": ["Rinca", "Flores", "Gili Motang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You may remember this fictional actor from such films within films as Eenie Meeni Miney, Die, The Revenge of Abe Lincoln or perhaps Good-Time Slim, Uncle Doobie, and the Great Frisco Freak-Out.", "correct_answer": "Troy McClure", "incorrect_answers": ["Ed Wood", "Roger Corman", "Russ Meyer"]}]